http://www.salesianhigh.org/privacy-policy/

Google Login
Search for:
OUR SIGNATURE SYMBOLS
The heart with the flame represents charity.
OUR SIGNATURE SYMBOLS
The anchor serves to remind us that Salesian is our home and we are all anchored here.
OUR SIGNATURE SYMBOLS
The star represents guidance like the north star to guide us.
OUR SIGNATURE SYMBOLS
The cross serves to remind us of the value of a christian education.
OUR SIGNATURE SYMBOLS
The vessel represents knowledge.
Privacy Policy
Salesian High School is dedicated to making your online experience convenient and safe. We define “personal information” as data about an identifiable individual, which may include name, address, telephone number, email address or other information which may be used to identify someone, particularly as defined by privacy laws. By using our website, or providing us with your personal information in any way, you agree to accept the conditions stated in our Privacy Policy.
What kind of information do we collect?
We collect the personal information you provide when contacting us in any capacity.
How do we use your personal information?
We will use personal information collected from you for the following reasons:
Respond to your inquiries and provide customer service.
For conducting research.
To combat online identity theft and fraud.
How do we use cookies?
At this time, we use cookies only for providing a “remembered login” feature for user accounts.
Will we share your information with third parties?
We may share some personal information we have collected about you with third parties who perform services for us. For example, we use third-party vendors to host our website, manage our email distribution systems, print letters and mailings, authorize payments, and analyze data for marketing effectiveness. These service providers are given only the information they need to perform their assigned functions and are not authorized to use or disclose your personal information for their own purposes.
Is my personal information secure?
We have taken significant steps to ensure that all personal information entrusted to us is handled and stored through secure methods.
For more information about our Privacy Policy, please email us info@salesianhigh.org
Salesian High School is proud to be a part of the Catholic Schools of the Archdiocese of New York.
SALESIAN HIGH SCHOOL
148 East Main StreetNew Rochelle, NY 10801Phone: (914) 632-0248Email: info@salesianhigh.org
Salesian High School is proud to be a part of the Catholic Schools of the Archdiocese of New York.
© 2020 Salesian High School, All Rights Reserved
